I do wonder if sort of the timing of all
this stuff is just going to play out
kind of like it historically has where
you know and if you think about it
silver silver has actually done
essentially
what I was more inclined to think that
Bitcoin would do right I mean if you
look at silver's lows silver had its
first low uh in you know sort of here
you can see in in February when was
Bitcoin's low
February. Okay, that was one low and
then it had another low here in in
March. So, you basically had like a Q1
low and then you had a summer low and
then it's coming down into Q4, right? I
mean, it's basically what we talked
about with Bitcoin, but Bitcoin did not
have this type of move. And you could
argue it was because Bitcoin topped on
apathy rather than euphoria.